arabelove.com 2018-01-31

# Arab Marriage friendship zawaj love arablove, arab singles, arab dating, arabic, arab personals, single muslim, dating arab girls, muslim dating, arab chat, chatting, muslim dating service, single muslim women, arab women, arabic christian -arab-dating-privacy:: arabelove.com

THIS AGREEMENT WAS LAST UPDATED ON June 20, 2010. 

arabelove.com is firmly committed to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website, including the arabelove.com communities. 

The protection of your privacy being very important, we have adopted the following practices to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal information. We will notify all registered users via email of any material change to this Privacy Statement, unless you have opted-out of receiving email from us. From time to time, changes to this Privacy Statement will also be communicated on this site.

**What information do you gather automatically from visitors?**

We use your IP address (the series of numbers associated with your individual computer) to help us maintain our site and identify problems with our server. Your IP address does not disclose any personally revealing information about you. 

We do use cookies to identify traffic that comes through advertising and to facilitate a more user friendly experience. Cookies are small pieces of information that a Website places on your computer's hard drive so we know it's you when you visit. This helps us to create a personalized experience for you when you visit our site. The use of cookies is a very common practice on the Internet. If you are uncomfortable with this, you can disable all cookies through your browser settings. Your enjoyment of our site won't be affected if you have set your browser to reject cookies.

**What information will you ask me for?**

When you register to use any arabelove.com service you will be asked for some general identifying information which will enable us to provide you with this individualized service. We gather contact information (like your email address), demographic information (like your city of residence or age). We may share some of this information for our own research purposes with our professional advisors or consultants and third party partners, however the information shared will be limited to non-personally identifying demographic information shared under cover of a confidentiality agreement. 

Once you have registered, you will be given the option of creating a pseudonymous profile (nickname and personal description) within our communities where your gender is applicable. You will be asked for some personal but non-identifying information to complete your profile (i.e. whether you have dependants, height, body type, race, religion, whether you smoke, etc). This information is not linked in any way to your personally identifiable information, for other members to see. Obviously, if you provide us with a photograph some of your information may become personally identifiable information.

**How will this information be used and who has access to it?**

If you choose to have them sent to you, we may use your contact information to send you valuable updates and timely notices of promotions and mailbox status reports. Our site provides you with the opportunity to opt-in to receiving different types of communications from us at the point where we request registration information. You may modify this choice at any time by selecting "Account" from the member home page. We reserve the right to use your contact information at any time to advise you of any updates that may materially affect your rights or status on our site.

Your non-personally identifying demographic information is used to personalize your experience, allow other members to find you through a search, to compose your personal profile - which is associated with a pseudonymous identity you have created - and to deliver targeted advertising and promotional offers to you from external companies that are of the highest relevance to your demographic profile. Other than your arabelove.com mail box, your contact information is never available to other members or organizations. 

The personally identifiable information we collect from you is used for internet review and to improve the content and functionality of our web server or customize the layout of our pages for each individual member. The specific information we collect is not shared with other organizations and we will never release your personally identifiable information to an external organization without your prior consent except for the purposes of validating credit information and collecting debts. We may disclose your personally identifiable information if we reasonably believe we are required to do so by operation of law, which may include, but is not limited to a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on arabelove.com .

Although arabelove.com makes use of up to date technology in order to protect your pictures from being copied or captured by unauthorized third parties, please keep in mind that we cannot ensure complete protection. 

**How long do you keep the information I've given you?**   
We keep the information you have given us for as long as you are a member on the site or for as long as we are required to do so by law, which ever is longer..

**Can I change the information I have already given you?**

You can always verify or request the removal of the personally identifiable information we have collected and change your registration information by selecting "Account" from the main menu on the site. 

**Do you monitor online behavior?**

Our members communicate with each other through instant messages and onsite mail. While we do not, as a rule, moderate or monitor members' private exchanges, we reserve the right to do so if we suspect users of being under 18 or of using our service for the purpose of solicitation or any other violation of our terms of use or Privacy Statement. Member submissions that appear on the public area of the site are moderated and, if necessary, we reserve the right to edit, delete, remove or not use any communication on a public area of the site. 

Members may choose to participate in community polls. The results of these polls are tracked by gender only and do not reveal any personal identifiable information linked to the individual voters.

**What security features do you have?**

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. 

**Advertisers**

When you inquire about advertising opportunities on our site, you will be asked for contact information and information related to your advertising objectives. This information will be used to provide you with the business information you are seeking. Your information is only shared with internal staff and the external ad representation agencies that sell media space on the site, on our behalf. arabelove.com sites may contain links to other sites not affiliated with arabelove.com . Please note that these other sites may have privacy policies that differ from those of arabelove.com . We have no control over any personal information that you provide to these sites.

We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads on our behalf. These companies may employ cookies and action tags (also known as single pixel gifs or web beacons) to measure advertising effectiveness. Any information that these third parties collect via cookies and action tags is completely anonymous.

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. 
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet. 
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [ Google ad and content network privacy policy](https://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [ click here](https://www.networkadvertising.org/).

©arabelove.com, 2010.
